A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit gates (Box 1137, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Legal (Box 1137, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Liquidation (Box 1137, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 1137, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1137, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Plantings (Box 1137, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark (Box 1138, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Playhouse (Box 1138, Folder 2-4)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Review Committee (Box 1138, Folder 5, Box 1139, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Property (Box 1139, Folder 2-4, Box 1140, Folder 1-4, Box 1141, Folder 1-5, Box 1142, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Property (Box 1143, Folder 1-5, Box 1144, Folder 1-4, Box 1145, Folder 1-6, Box 1146, Box 1147, Folder 1-3, Box 1148)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor (Box 1149, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - A-Z (Box 1149, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Maine - General Correspondence (Box 1149, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Proposed Seal Harbor Foundation (Box 1149, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Acadia Corp. (Box 1149, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Asti-Kim Corporation (Box 1149, Folder 7-8, Box 1150, Folder 1-5, Box 1151, Box 1152, Folder 1-8, Box 1153, Folder 1-4, Box 1154)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Budget (Box 1155, Folder 1-3, Box 1156, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Equipment (Box 1156, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Expenditures (Box 1156, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Finances (Box 1156, Folder 5-6)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Maps (Box 1157, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Mount Desert Development Corp (Box 1157, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Mount Desert Summer-Year Round Resident Planning Committee (Box 1157, Folder 3-5, Box 1158, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - General Correspondence (Box 1158, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - A-Z (Box 1159, Folder 1-5)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Acadia National Park (Box 1159, Folder 6, Box 1160, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Land Purchases (Box 1160, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Land Sales (Box 1160, Folder 4-11, Box 1161, Folder 1-15)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Rental Houses (Box 1161, Folder 16-17)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Seaside Inn (Box 1161, Folder 18)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Trust (Box 1161, Folder 19)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Planning (Box 1162, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Property - Rockefeller, Abby A. Gardens (Eyrie Gardens) (Box 1162, Folder 2-5, Box 1163, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Hills Realty - Greenrock Corporation - Seal Harbor - Seal Harbor Water Company (Box 1163, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Interstate North (Box 1163, Folder 4-5, Box 1164, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Kahuku Venture - Printed Material (Box 1164, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Kahuku Venture (Box 1165, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation (Box 1165, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Construction - Contractors (Box 1165, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency (Box 1166, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Clippings (Box 1166, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Cost and Cash Flow Projections (Box 1166, Folder 4, Box 1167, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Change Orders (Box 1167, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Finances (Box 1167, Folder 4-5, Box 1168, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Printed Material (Box 1168, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Overlook and Ramp Construction (Box 1168, Folder 3, Box 1170, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Loews L'Enfant Plaza Hotel (Box 1168, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1168, Folder 5, Box 1169, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Directors Meetings (Box 1169, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Opening (Box 1169, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Progress Reports (Box 1170, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - Subscription Calls (Box 1170, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - L'Enfant Plaza Corporation - West Building (Box 1170, Folder 4-7)
  - Real Estate - Morningside Heights Inc. (Box 1171, Folder 1-3, Box 1172, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Morningside Heights Inc. - Housing Corporation (Box 1172, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Morningside Heights Inc. - Planner Position (Box 1172, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Morningside Heights Inc. - Contributions (Box 1172, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Morningside Heights Inc. - Printed Material (Box 1173, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Mountain Park (Box 1174, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Mutual Real Estate Investment Trust (Box 1174, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. (Named changed to Westbay Community Associates) (Box 1174, Folder 3-4, Box 1175, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Articles (Box 1176, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Board of Directors (Box 1176, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Clippings (Box 1176, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Expenditures (Box 1176, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Ideal Basic Industries (merger) (Box 1177, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Legal (Box 1177, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Lindquist memos (Box 1177, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1177, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Meyers, Andre (Box 1177, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Printed Material (Box 1177, Folder 6, Box 1178, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Public Affairs (Box 1178, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc. - Stock Subscription (Box 1178, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates (Formerly Pacific Air Commerce Center) - A-Z (Box 1178, Folder 4-6, Box 1179, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates (Formerly Pacific Air Commerce Center Inc.) (Box 1179, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Clippings (Box 1179, Folder 3, Box 1180, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Coyote Point (Box 1180, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Dilworth J. Richardson (Box 1180, Folder 3, Box 1181, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Finances (Box 1181, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Jericho Bay (Box 1181, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Legal (Box 1182, Folder 1-3, Box 1183, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Miscellaneous (Box 1184, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Mariners Island (Box 1184, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Memoranda (Box 1184, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1184, Folder 4-5)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Partners Meetings (Box 1184, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Property Proposals (Box 1184, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Public Affairs (Box 1185, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Sale of Partnership Interest (Box 1185, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - San Bruno Mountain Land (Box 1185, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Tartan Bay, Inc. (Box 1185, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Trip File (Box 1185, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Westbay Community Associates - Visitacion Rancho (Box 1186, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Panola Associates (Fairington) (Box 1186, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Panola Associates (Fairington) - Finances and Partnership Agreements (Box 1187, Folder 1-5, Box 1188, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - A-O (Box 1189, Folder 1-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - P-Z (Box 1190, Folder 1-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - A-R (Box 1191, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - S-Z (Box 1192, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Articles (Box 1192, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - By-Laws (Box 1192, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - JDR Jr Plaque - Prededication (Box 1192, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Board of Directors (Box 1192, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Budget Statements (Box 1192, Folder 6-7, Box 1193, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Centerscope Publication (Box 1193, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Columbia Lease (Box 1194, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Contributions (Box 1194, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Dilworth Correspondence (Box 1194, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees (Box 1194, Folder 4-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Twenty and Thirty Year Club (Box 1194, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exxon Building (Box 1195, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances (Box 1195, Folder 2-4, Box 1196, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Annual Reports (Box 1196, Folder 4-5, Box 1197, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Financial Statements (Box 1197, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Future (Box 1197, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Audits (Box 1198, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Securities (Box 1198, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Chase Manhattan Bank Trusts (Box 1198, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal (Box 1198, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Tishman Construction and Research (Box 1198, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances - Investments (Box 1199, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Luncheon Club (Box 1200, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1200, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finance Committee Meetings (Box 1200, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Passes (Box 1200, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Printed Material (Box 1201, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio City Music Hall (Box 1201, Folder 3, Box 1202, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center - Rock-McGraw, Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1202, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - JDR Jr. Plaque - A-Z (Box 1202, Folder 4-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center - Rock-Americas, Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1203, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Celanese (Box 1203, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Celanese - Finances (Box 1203, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Brothers Lease (Box 1203, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-McGraw Inc. - Project Y (Box 1203, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-McGraw Inc. - Budget (Box 1203, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Real Estate Taxes (Box 1204, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Sinclair, Inc. (Box 1204, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time (Box 1204, Folder 4-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time - Financial Statements (Box 1205, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time - Finances (Box 1204, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time - Meetings (Box 1205, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. (Box 1206, Folder 1-3)
    Open in 2027
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Employees (Box 1206, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Finances (Box 1206, Folder 5-7)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Securities (Box 1207, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Annual Plan (Box 1207, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1207, Folder 3-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - New York Hilton (Box 1207, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - New York Hilton - Construction Work (Box 1208, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - New York Hilton - Finances (Box 1208, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time Inc. - Finances (Box 1208, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc - New York Hilton - Opening (Box 1208, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock Hill-Uris Inc. - Sperry Rand (Box 1208, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time Participation in XYZ - Dilworth Office (Box 1208, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Projects X, Y, Z (Box 1209, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Standard Oil Building - Project X (Box 1209, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Standard Oil Building - Finances (Box 1209, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - A-G (Box 1210, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - H-Z (Box 1211, Folder 1-5, Box 1212, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Agreements between LSR/Eastern Airlines (Box 1212, Folder 4, Box 1213, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Board of Directors (Box 1212, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Eastern Airlines (Box 1213, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Ferries (Box 1213, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Finances (Box 1213, Folder 4-5)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Memos (Box 1213, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1214, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Personnel (Box 1214, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Printed Material (Box 1214, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Releases (Box 1214, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Cerromar Hotel (Box 1214, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Cerromar Hotel - Opening (Box 1215, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Contributions (Box 1215, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach (Box 1215, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach - Public Affairs (Box 1215, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach - Roads (Box 1215, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach - Dorado Properties (Box 1215, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach - Dorado Beach Golf and Tennis Club (Box 1215, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach - Dorado Beach Hotel Corporation (Box 1216, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay (Box 1216, Folder 2-3, Box 1217, Folder 1-2, 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Board of Trustees (Box 1217, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Maps (Box 1217, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Opening (Box 1217, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - A-Z (Box 1218, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel (Box 1218, Folder 3, Box 1219, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Kawaihae Kona Highway (Box 1220, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Memos (Box 1220, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Olohana (Box 1220, Folder 3, Box 1221, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Printed Material (Box 1220, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill (Box 1221, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Waimea (Box 1221, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Water (Box 1221, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Works of Art (Box 1222, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mt. Tom (Box 1222, Folder 2-4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mt. Tom - Contributions (Box 1222, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - Mt. Tom - Snow Engineering Report (Box 1222, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - St. Croix Project (Box 1223, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - St. Croix Project - Agreement (Box 1223, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - St. Croix Project - Clippings (Box 1223, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - St. Croix Project - Finances (Box 1223, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Rockresorts - St. Croix Project - General Correspondence (Box 1223, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - West 55th St. Rockefeller Garage (Box 1224, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Offers - A-B (Box 1224, Folder 2-4)
  - Real Estate - Offers - C-E (Box 1225, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - E-H (Box 1226, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - H-L (Box 1227, Folder 1-4)
  - Real Estate - Offers - L-R (Box 1228, Folder 1-3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - O-Z (Box 1229, Folder 1-4, Box 1230, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Bishop Ranch (Box 1230, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Doelger Properties - San Mateo, Calif (Box 1230, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Dominguez Estate (Box 1230, Folder 4, Box 1231, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Douglas, Lewis, Jr. Rancho California (Box 1231, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - General Properties Corp. (Box 1231, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Exposition Company (Box 1232, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Investment Proposal memos (Box 1232, Folder 2-3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Modern Community Developers Inc. - Rosemary Apartments (Box 1232, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Offers - North Fulton Property (Box 1232, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Northlake Mall and Office Park - Valuations (Box 1233, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Parcel 8 Office Tower (Box 1233, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Peacock Gap (Box 1233, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Peacock Gap - Documents (Box 1233, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Peacock Gap - Financial (Box 1234, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Peacock Gap - Printed material (Box 1234, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate - Offers - Pickands Mather Co. (Box 1234, Folder 3)
  - Religion - A (Box 1234, Folder 4-5)
  - Religion - A-C (Box 1235, Folder 1-3)
  - Religion - C-E (Box 1236, Folder 1-4)
  - Religion - D-I (Box 1237, Folder 1-4)
  - Religion - I-L (Box 1238, Folder 1-4)
  - Religion - L-N (Box 1239, Folder 1-3)
  - Religion - O-S (Box 1240, Folder 1-3)
  - Religion - S-W (Box 1241, Folder 1-4)
  - Religion - W-Z (Box 1242, Folder 1-2)
  - Religion - Academy of Religion and Mental Health (Box 1242, Folder 3-4)
  - Religion - Academy of Religion and Mental Health - Printed Material (Box 1242, Folder 5)
  - Religion - American Bible Society (Box 1243, Folder 1-2)
  - Religion - American Friends Service Committee (Box 1243, Folder 3-4)
  - Religion - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (Box 1244, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Brotherhood in Action, Inc. (Box 1244, Folder 2)
  - Religion - Christian Fellowship Foundation Inc. (Box 1244, Folder 3)
  - Religion - Christian Fellowship Foundation, Inc. - Packard Manse (Box 1244, Folder 4)
  - Religion - Church League of America (Box 1244, Folder 5)
  - Religion - Congress on the Spiritual Values of Tourism (Box 1245, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Council for Religion in Independent Schools (Box 1245, Folder 2-3)
  - Religion - Council of Churches of the City of NY (Box 1245, Folder 4-5)
  - Religion - Council of Churches of the City of New York - Society for the Family Man (Box 1245, Folder 6)
  - Religion - Council of Churches of Greater Washington (Box 1246, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Episcopal Society for Cultural and Racial Unity (Box 1246, Folder 2)
  - Religion - Graham, Billy NY Crusade (Box 1246, Folder 3)
  - Religion - Harold Institute (Box 1246, Folder 4)
  - Religion - Institutes of Religion and Health (Box 1246, Folder 5)
  - Religion - Interchurch Center (Box 1246, Folder 6)
  - Religion - Interfaith Movement Inc. (Box 1247, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Moral Rearmament (Box 1247, Folder 2)
  - Religion - National Conference of Christian & Jews (Box 1247, Folder 3-4)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S - A-Z (Box 1247, Folder 5-6)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - A Christian Ministry w/Peace in Leisure Recreation (Box 1248, Folder 1)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. (Box 1248, Folder 2)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - Commission on Religion and Race (Box 1248, Folder 3)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - Taos Indians (Box 1248, Folder 4)
  - Religion - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - Task Force on Leisure (Box 1248, Folder 5)
  - Religion - Protestant Council of the City of New York (Box 1249, Folder 1)
  - Religion - Protestant Council of the City of New York - Family Man Awards (Box 1249, Folder 2)
  - Religion - Seamans Church Institute (Box 1249, Folder 3-4)
  - Religion - Temple of Understanding (Box 1249, Folder 5)
  - Religion - World Center for Liturgical Studies (Box 1249, Folder 6)
  - Religion - World Council of Churches (Box 1249, Folder 7)
  - Religion - Churches - A (Box 1249, Folder 8)
  - Religion - Churches - A-C (Box 1250, Folder 1-4)
  - Religion - Churches - C-E (Box 1251, Folder 1-4)